Guide to the Richard W. Robinson papers, 1957-1998
Richard W. Robinson papers, 1957-1998
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Richard W. Robinson papers, 1957-1998
21-41-3428
1 cubic ft.
Notes, reports, tests, and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence and field trial data concerning plant breeding.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor in the Dept. of Horticultural Sciences at the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, with a speciality in genetics and breeding of vegetable crops.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence and field trial data concerning plant breeding.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
New York State Agricultural Experiment Station--Faculty.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Agriculture--Study and teaching.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station. Dept. of Horticultural Sciences.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Virus Test Results, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Virus Test Results, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Virus Test Results, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Virus Test Results, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Virus Test Results, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Virus Test Results, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Virus Test Results, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Virus Test Results, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CMV of Lettuce (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Breeding Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Plant Intro. of Lettuce, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ASGROW Vegetable Seeds (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Andras Andrasfalvy, 1969-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: B, 1957-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Annual Review, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Variety Trial Candidates and Results, 1977-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Saligna (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lettuce (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Mutants of Lettuce (Box 1, Folder 19)
- E.M.S. Lettuce (Box 1, Folder 20)
- V.T. Lettuce Trials (Box 1, Folder 21)
- B.C. Status Summary (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Virus Resistant Lettuce (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Root Rot Test (Box 1, Folder 24)
- History of Lettuce (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Broad Bean Wilt Virus (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Aspen Yellow (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Downy Mildew Data (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Seeds to Test (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Notes, Tests (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Summary of Results (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Nematode Tests (Box 1, Folder 32)
- "Cucurbita the fascinating genus of squash, pumpkin, and gourds" by R.W. Robinson and Paris Trail (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1971-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Tomato Pectins and Viscosity (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Tests, by Dr. Robinson, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Pre-Robinson Tomato Yield, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Tomato Yields, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Tomato Yields, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Tomato Yields, Antroz Test Data, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Tomato Yields, Antroz Test Data, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Tomato Yields, Antroz Test Data, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous Test Data (Box 1, Folder 44)